We're. Moving in the.
First. Ever member.
Of the. World.
The all.
And often
a soldier died and has been using nested
lacks for disarmament Chilcotin often is
that
a week ago is this particular night and he
came home on leave Well that's one thing
that is another little there are
a number of the greats over the world been
forgotten Michael despised not so by the
way when this is still not much of
a crime. To get the old.
Man the bike will sell and
go you'll be like get
a little. Red Coals make of what the.
All right.
With that what's the meaning of all this
where you didn't go to the said new look.
I don't know what your name is you can call
me on ice commission no officer didn't
you know I did have
a crossing from Excellent thank you but
if I'm not in that landing in that I was
dead that he said because isn't that heavy
annoying because if you've seen this.
What's it like know that. This
nation is that is this. What that
means is the confidant the audience of
a sentence like shield of the out of the
mind when I question to let it in the
sense that it's up to this extent
these particular people it's
a because I don't see no you won't see if
you keep on talking now Johnny is making
every effort at the moment to buy up.
Something you love your country and I just
you can't guess why. But I'm
waiting for you to tell me.
These areas always upset the Gulf and it
was still is I'm. Hearing about the one
British one American who
has a reputation of being
a sort of verbal of light. Action to me
yes they demanded Brody was much too well
known for our presence up here when you're
driving Ashenden is going to Switzerland
to locate
a certain German agent was leaving for
Arabia that is shortly by Constantinople
description. Let's hope.
That your predecessor still.
In his last message said he thought he was
saying the hotel except I want you to go
there now in this envelope is the name of
a man playing for both sides or may help
you to find him when I have found him.
That sounded just like
a pistol shot didn't report to me and you
were given further instructions. To say.
He's not to be allowed to respond
precisely. Like a man who makes
a quick decision and I think I would take
it to do the change in the cities on the
destroyer which would take across the
channel they are going to switch them by
around about their systems over there
before. I'd have this number and then the
second thing is
a very useful what we call in the head is
to make the whole wide cheaper because
you've got
a lot of Callahan and in the mix of that
you can call in the general on the job of
picking
a company didn't itself that was again off
the top of the cellar so when they began
on it you can't there's
no fashionable even
a few minutes they get.
Right but I kept that.
Now bear in mind that this is this No it's
up to those of you in the job but do I
what. Yes they did my
girl does that say they don't have an
upstairs you know I got to get an apartment
out to some people. The general I did you
an injustice I thought you came down here
to dodge the bombs but we did
a lot of you should know what that is
actionable in them from what is some of the
law because in con they don't do very
pretty good may have some very important
business here in St Guillen and I would
be very very. I love your medical and
other ladies. So now that you've met we're
going to tell you the Parthenon I don't
see what he's up.
I'm.
Telling.
You. That really with. What I'm actually.
Action there or yes you are over two
hundred fifty four in five seconds
a lot of it will manage to do it when you
sign your name and you are right about
that or the first letter that you know
that much and then as it is this isn't
a private thought. I done got
a wife should I get that day you would not
disagree with the soon. I know not quite
the same kind of button to press
on isn't it did yes miss you.
Is that an interview well mother and I
become the few that is not in the. Minimum
is not. Going on upstairs rooms could
see four to five you said yes I suppose
a Mrs action has
a key to the kid. No no no I think I'll
just surprise it on my own if you don't
mind Come I like to know what you said
if it's one of those numbers again two
hundred fifty four and five I've got
them down for yourself and give them
a. Backdrop.
Well. The way I found so far is
a bit of an Gollum I felt quite
right then translated Not
a bit better. Or oh boy thank you
Mrs Miller Frantically she got home
canning someone just thought of his food
my idea that all the things. In the news
that yeah it's.
Actually true that bad guys know.
What I'm going to do tomorrow.
Right you going out with me and
you're promised. What about
a nice private technican the world
around in some way. Holding did not make
any bearing it with you
now. I. Know that means
a body economic quite as well by the
overweight. Looking for anybody around here
my wife. A divorce that
looks like I am addressing
the guilty. Are your heroes in the
manger how well you're looking
a little I've been lonely Oh no this can't
go on I had to get up and then I guess
they didn't say yes a
good angel through with
a Gilligan most times and then told Mr
Godzilla must admit it sounds well the way
you say it that is really Robert Mark
of this medium in the locket and it was
fashioned and the. Allies of the time now
the triangle to retire from the family
circle existed back.
I wasn't making you guys into
There are gathered there are
a good guy that any future plans about now
understand who you are what your name is
and why you're passing is about as my wife
my name is Alfa tatting I suppose you
could have asked the other
question yourself but to me that
a rough you are going to unload you on me
elegantly put it but on the same job Yes
ours and for me time it come out
here to join my husband through
a good action the one I have the media to
how do I know you are really the person
you say you are. Here's my passport
that's that or. Was it all of
you can download. Anything else
first of all I'd like to see
your that's better still.
All right as knowledge your is my
true north pole. Why that is the you
in my bedroom are bedroom by you.
Then it is you.
Well what does it say. You
might I come in you know
a little adult again you don't mind my
getting over the days where none of the
leads to. How do I
get out is in code I know you have news
to me. Rather concerned who says I'm
making you
a madman just to round off your new
character but as you say your wife comes of
fighting the stark and they get
a little foggy to inject. I look to you
directly and it isn't the right channel be
as connubial as possible yours are others
CAN YOU FEEL ME still hear me begin live
affectionate no big way out
much in the. Well what is
a given you have been an exam
a surprise Thank you. And you are believing
above yes yes I saw the picture you
have
a video gentleman from is about as I thought
that's very kind of you. I think of me
then I don't even have any footing on your
face but what do you really think that
John got what else was going to do
was another thing you may have been
unnecessarily They had
a menacing angel. I converse with them first
real you think I'm going to give you.
The means to an end then being psychic
degrees they will get happiness on
you all that sort of a man
a quite amusing if you think I live here
let's understand each other identify those
I call the dozens of people to come out
here to do something worthwhile there's no
good just standing there looking middle
aged and bleating about Alright alright
alright. That's how do you
stop I got are going to have
a gavel and this he said You
tell me the rest that's that.
Handel good to hear Maggie you're our friend
because we can see you again yesterday
on oh I have since I have you being on the
time I got you all right all right to
take it easy take it easy How did you get
in I was thinking on the door all the
time but and I was knocking and barking but
you did nothing to beat the company of
beauties woman Lady you know other than
do that so I knew the country out of me
probably about the hotel and tried to show
me some silly thing very nice to. Your
wife how do you know that is my wife. Very
simply that's part of him David each one
and said to each other once you know like
I knew other you know of course I do is
one of our colleagues on your general
gender bump in your most intimate in a big
a big On the day long book that said before
you and I met so that you would want
this lady is not my wife and what this lady
even if you to me officially by old men
oh yes what do you mean when
you. Like the fact that well
or you you mean given to you. For the
much include you know do you really you
think me who has given her or maybe perhaps
he's almost all of these I don't worry
about of. Oh I think that's
really too much for you
if we want it but for me or to think
not what the map you know. Maybe you.
Think that means. You know.
As a. You know better listen
if you like than if Brody was
a bachelor that's what Ashenden has to be
a married man it makes it much safer that
all this goes in it's you to me it's part
of my disguise. She's nothing to me I
tell you and I'm nothing to her got you
understand nor marriage or maybe
because here is lies true
but of course as to what you mean though
Danny in this case may be the affections
of the very. Complete
reason absolutely as I'm
concerned hard to do anything about this
do I look as if I enjoy conjuring trick
general no lovemaking no fight it is we
can't afford to take risks to put police at
the others in no time so you gotta get
a move on what you've done they've got
to get away. You much gentlemen in
the process of creating I dare
say the middleman you were given
a purpose we've got to start
tomorrow others job is to go to
a village in the mountains calling in the
inland out of the church and that church
we are badly organised to ourselves here
have been working for the Germans but is
now on our side we've got to get in touch
with him and you know put it on the back
of the matter and after that why you
left and you stay here and wait to get
a phone call come to thank you never get
a good time to move your friends line you
know my dress go on general Out you go.
Well well how did you get wasn't enough
now that I did it all began the are in
special benefit that I kind of I
was up the front of his I'm just.
Married that has to get all right chat about
that about your life doesn't give you
got
a job to do and it's part of that job to
keep it secret whatever happened. Yes
.
Look at. These.
United fans. Are not insisting.
The spanking for.
This one because I can't make them angry.
I don't want the other side.
Strapped Nice work me very me
someone very much did not want we should
speak to keep the but it looks like
doesn't. Old look well we're.
Not so nice after all big struggle
before you've got me back
a much better see the middle of
this is the man feeling yet though.
Listen if you are so he's the man we are
looking for to find the right that's in
that is one way of stopping at the
let's not forget some of coming.
Up.
All. This so.
It will work with the new who's. Who
the room who the shooter who
lose it to is the it to my lady
the that one the the one in
the girl even in the
room of the room where.
The food.
I think that's
a little longer I don't want to come and
speak and I said I think Charlie the bread
you might moving down a bit so we can
see the scenery. I was guilty of at
a distance but yours aren't I
never thought to look with.
You mind hold on for me to get. A. Look
at that nose. Well I bet you could
squeeze and get
a quarter whiskey out of. A stamp
your. Emissions mostly. Smoke
. There are government you know only.
You from now here I was afraid
of that no you don't understand.
To go to go region now complete country
part of this strange power you
have
a culture and. No mystery lady just the
well equipped young man at home in every
language bad language while
you all. MANPAD alive when
a bus strike woman. For the matter
when now love want to get by
not speaking of love you think that building
it has been your the mind of like it's
laid out according to you to Bali Oh well
if you want me getting mad about you out
of levels. Speaking of your husband if you
go on defending him like that the idea
might get around to loving
I think I get. Along
that's been going on since yesterday yesterday
that's after finding out the way you
practically flung yours now that
my last call the police had.
Nothing. On James I mean
a casino. You played with. Diablo
she's nothing dining out of where can she
be I don't know I'm sure the matter with
me still Bryan Bender is here all right
all right come down to the condo probably
middle somewhere. I'm going to do that in
the living Madam I'm going to get out of
get the bill to the cathedral to get
a boy. Can
some channels. Find manuals and have
them have jobs it's good casino
to see nice Incidentally one
hundred people model that is
a generalization you aren't going to jump
in conclusions maybe nine because S.
Is found out something here let's go steady
on because I'm going to so they were
a little bit of going to.
Again I chip today yes. And I
guess yes. Your own money. All right.
What is. The good. I can other
than to spend to stand between you and I
are going to raise we settle down together
but these days. I can.
Do this in
a big way. Oh look at the
dog I put on there tell me.
Who the better the militancy.
Is like it's exactly how I hate our dogs.
You must have had a number of I got on
a board tell me how does I cannot hear.
You don't mind if you haven't been
a good eight nine of them what do you think
of that thank heavens you come along so
I can tell wife of mine and I'm tired of
talking in words of one syllable. Oh you
don't know each other do you this is the
gentleman I was talking to about the bunny
. Gentle pumping you must assume
a debate here they come they don't.
Mind if I call you Charlie. I meant.
To buy me what I think my winning.
Would have been without.
Some total days' work.
That's
a lot of buttons for somebody to have to
pay seven buttons on just I don't. I want
to go to. The same as those nasty things.
I think that stuck out in the middle of
the dog was tied up in front of me. More
than. Enough to know my
mama have to. Give me.
That just I don't. Think it quite.
Well I don't like about that
are you. Going to keep your.
Head I'm going to continue
to be able to say
a little shouldn't have he ended up in
politics my and was already without him and
so I think it's my hope. Which it is the
sense of anybody who. Couldn't fight
nobody to try to make you mad because that's
about don't be what the noble thought
it sounded back to the regulation could
have many of all of them I guess. Are these
regulations governed by the Geneva Convention
because. They are like lessons of the
casino and you got a copy of the regs
don't need our well known he hasn't got
a copy of the rules it's Jennifer Aniston
the low services for that us that we
allow to have a dog
unless unless you show us
a copy of the regulations governing the
fence what is the life of an upright I
would do the whole thing over again if you
want to do that now hell he needed it.
And then peace and peace it becomes. A
kiss to save lives stop are dozens of.
Times that if you say without
little regard that I'm
a good girl and I mean people at my desk
when I wipe you know I do it again or they
. Can at the pump. You must admit that
a big open mic you also have an aversion
to YES ME friend of every man can use that
in mind I'm going to my wife and what he
does I think is cause for celebration
anybody here on the wagon
Well I'll be good for
a party kind of things and I think I know
this about language and I think you're
entitled of our strength along. With
you he was in theme village to they've
even gone because of this
carnage boy no simpatico what.
You were starting on a long trip today
a day off tomorrow. In
the book you must assume
a little bit get the country they don't
want to get my way. I think you've
already made. Them look at the price
that we're going to. Live in the day
after tomorrow friend of yours and I want
to have you been away from England now.
And never been through.
A double agent on it but if
you're to cut the matter
a little general that's quite enough it is
not enough for me just beginning. About
And I spent a little break put
it together general to make
a speech of you have. A What's the trouble
me not. The thing it's all perfectly all
right I'm not
a critic not all night schemes some mean
VERY be great to see the thing is nothing
I see the thing is very big something you
bet you are. Not generally known and I
know I make the perp with that we should
climb the mountain all together he think
me not keep our mountain climb. When Because
I only think can you people remember
that it's to my editor All I said was you
couldn't go climbing out of the thinking
of Little Women with that sure that all
jelly was only joking forget it on the
computer the fact is matter never
mind. I've. Always found it
I think man mountain much higher think
you got this obsession I wanted all the
blood out of the traditional say just
like you feel you see you see he's making
a camp out. In the back down
to that then. The bed is all
right I'll find
a little gentleman fight that all the doubt
about that they would get about. The
Lang and L.
Committing come along and. Their other to
keep it two. Thousand feet of understanding
. Of what I want to do about it the
tallow is going to guy. But you know the.
Old bottle neck. And that affected I one
going to leave the day after tomorrow
effect picking up myself. That
would have an awful lot of.
Opposition. Got covered else.
So you couldn't get them
out of the. Math but I could of course
but how about you get this when breaking
a definite plan what does one climb
Mount the middle of night well
a guided engage while avoidable but I think
what about that the only car I get for
those old fashioned wise. That
is the most good as I give.
You one and. When you make it it will
likely barbequing tell one that you enjoyed
it in
a way to protect them if you know you would
become one of the biggest. OK whatever
I look at them is good. But somebody's
got to give an occupied what effect is
German conversation with my God I
can't breathe out of it so. I got
a family to come the old house
pass my new car come to the night.
Going to something. Done
hunting up of landing
a man. Can only remember the one who I know
I wanted the job to do it but I'm going
to being. All you can see and it is funny.
The you.
Thank.
You.
As I have been to get
a good man. In. Is
this your home. Where you
live of all the world if you
please do not talk about us
to go. Down as you would have
a different job on the things you
I'd love to. Do you I've read
very little. To do you say
to me the days of the big.
PAC money Kyle DNS pass me Val. The
cleanup of the board I feel done
done more with gas you die happy.
Please ma'am my mommy says if you room for
a new boy in your class never go away from
me I was speaking of the teacher do you
understand gentleman commanding not
a word by speak exactly I said done here
by this little girl. I promise to be good
I'll probably hear anything much here
a girl should smoke cigarettes that
would you like to tie it please the is
a busy condemning your. Song targets
Montagna. The Wilds of.
New York to the next the Asian
is the I thought of look what it
done of the dogs.
Oh you want to be back in camp good times
dinner whatever diet you have generally
sure you're really have big
fun when the thing is over.
Now the hats you are going to need today
and you wish to engage. In vast These are
duty I would say I want to double better
than that to myself my beautiful wife this
is my beautiful wife you look at these two
Mr Ashton what would you say I would say
I want
a single role. Is meant I'm proud to. Mr
. Weatherley going out to get your
version they're pretty good really I suppose
it all works child radio you know from
me just second nature. You got a grand
a voice. Is English men say the more
bitter the days the more bitter the BE
correct years approximately. Just to come.
Because it is always travel
in mouth disease in the.
Back cause. I know nothing.
Is not going to Israel will be happy.
For getting contraction of me that are
completely missing each. Besides what
about my money on the job what are you
waiting for. It's you do
Ballister that is he makes Again
the breakdown and I mean that and I'm
glad he's tired or to go if you are tired
it's gotta go good news or not this is
only three for me losing my bit or you won
your bet all right good I'll pay you the
money no but there is my honor to make the
climb or I've been going climbers up there
back here with me when you get to know
pretty pretty come with me you stay here
and then carry on alone I think I better
go with him to be tricky up there thank
you humans yes reach the top of the
observer he'll get them
on general rate. It's.
It's no use being
a very bad the most. It's
in your mask to come home after you. And
then this is happening here. Now you
lie down like
a good little duck. Now Mrs incentives
to go back to Agnes you've been to mass
this to much for your room
goes out to you. That you
do all right now right
now. Now you listen to me
thanks very much. It's
. I. Didn't And. You knew my
existence for I'm home.
It's. The kind of
a god sake. The
the. Yes I.
Told the girl. And sold the.
Loan. To.
All but
a quad plus. Some other. You
are nice to see but depends
how you're going to. Get the
Americans and that's the way I am. A.
Logo How do you. View me on
a good evening. Good evening
and what are you. Father
please let it go or fix something to fix
them in the few sequences in there he said
he said that's would not be able to move
forward and. ARE NOT IN THE MORE ABOUT of
nothing important only but not going to
Europe as well as when she was young and
photography or Britons reprinted
for at least one who Michelle A
east L.A.
The you the it auto the
I.A.E.A.
You ask for photographs I
have hundreds around for you which
you. Can do and I did not get all
the auto
the article to fit.
The of the first.
In the you.
You lay the it later
the auto the if.
I eat it all I it
auto It laid off the
it as it flew.
But.
The cop. The cop.
He was very much macros are
more common than Rico.
Early.
Polls in the papers and to be
a challenge. To the community Tom
even Monday I got the most special
I can get on the show and added to
those I Did they are obsessed. With.
Would like to tell you how no one dismissed
the meeting you dressed I just wonder
what you and I could post and I know I
didn't know think that looks old like you
try. To be said about
bullies. Like Seamus.
I could tell you. And enough to do with
this kind. Of discretion to discredit.
You you don't agree with. I've been spanked
by love for you because twenty five
kind I've been. I got
to open up to see the.
Oh so to the could and. Boring
being I did I was close I'm
gonna. Love that you'll be able to trick
the holding just told me job something
else. You update
a seller is basically as if I'm
doing it for money to no. Just.
You know it just to do that. And I.
Don't like just close quarters
and speak to. All men.
I don't like them much either
method I still don't make the top.
Doesn't mean much fun for
me either like the. One. I
didn't kill him you know. With
their one of the staff Oh yes I
was there all right. Half a
mile away at the other end of
a telescope. Yes it's quite true.
Just one of those long ranges that.
Doesn't make it any better but. I think
you are beginning to find that out too.
And you. Know I say don't cry you have
a cigarette. Why
can't you give it on us. That making
a difference to us. But
I won't use that it
was all over.
You know you weren't the only one that.
Someone's getting killed it's good.
It's.
Consistent with. That I thought I
mean that is that what it is almost
a pleasure to be alive is this the
distraction and I'm going there you're just
going to come out there.
It's just it is yes
it has Michael but then in another
business that is it is not
a resignation that this is going to get.
In the dollar that if these niggas it
especially the postscripts
and we're going to become this. We're going
to have let me get back to being for
nothing much just then somebody else got
to take my place that's all why doesn't
matter much due to this. Young president
I think that they are really.
Yes Oh that's the ugliest woman in
the world because you hated rival
all my good rivals but it
wasn't. Yes yes and much better
you know as all of. The big next to the
wise if you will. If you have not been
misunderstood it. Was pretty sad and then
the shattering shattering for get out
there. Oh I'm great I've gone
about some of my have been odd
who benefited me you know that. You
can cut out the Darby and Joan stuff
you see I know your husband and
look what you're passing up me
a caveman with a college
education. Or you want to have
a say in your life. Well
this is my last word listen.
Pardon me while the brain review. First
kids are my dad was not really you
yes my love not all that wants a what's
the idea but I've been kissing Oh Dani is
a little older. That you would
last let me get this straight move
I've been kissing you with the old
man. Oh well I'm satisfied now get
me. This madam is the end all and goodbye
and then you have quintupled you know I was
thought of that I believe you know it's
me oh hello General morning come to join
the celebration yes make the morning.
Exercise you know not this I'm getting
out of that one doesn't Bailey.
I ain't no no Legion It's just come to
a decision the most everybody does all
chordates they're going away to morrow it's
resign it's. Resigned What does his
work mean in middle of what impact the
bridge imaging could anger the bank he made
love want to make you quote out of me in
frontline would do this very same business
I wouldn't do it if I were in the
army fighting in the front lines
a band that can the job of this and
then the most I think. Does not
expect that me and. We not like
I don't think it's been what.
This look I'm fed up with this whole
business is not that we don't any good to be
not just so that's the I'm saying that and
I love what you mean like you know they
can quite easily find some of the much
better than we are they got it maybe for you
maybe for you than not for me justly very
well trained but after me we've got Black
Bloc lawyers I know all about that think
oh yes then it's good it's coming here and
you want to do what it allows and what I
am hearing the very big for you the best
to not say I did you like I meant the two
men to the right no making mistakes the
Bentley you know good number going I'm
really like you are you going to be me me
promise me do everything you only give
advice and Radovan I mean probably look at
my value get money up to the dollar Yes
it's done go all right I shall NOT
a few minutes action it's
sort of. I did it.
It's it's.
Thought.
To be just last year I'm in
a way yes but he is likely to babysit
also because it's well out. Much
hope it's good because of the time I
brought your very fine gentleman friend of
mine to see you all or what have you come
into my bedroom HAVE I BEEN SO I GOT How
do you do isn't she three pretty dark
Thank you. I don't think there's
a generalized but yes my private secret
guardian is going to three we all come on
come on general what's it all about very
very much all about you wait and see you
see last night we make I believe my
little baby game so we get the queen is
very creepy Of course you would we
also start out number one what about
a little conversation she tells me
about. What he had to own no no no
he worked in chocolate factory on the top
thoughts but he's in big money to make
the five times as big money as any other
club and he and I come to the point
companies. You go into pretty high
and then speak with the yes T.
Of the thing. You know. You see the
truck that factories not only factories but
the kids also and now you can see that
me very first convert me because you know
what you're no no no no I don't know it's
the big German spy or stuff it's like
getting custom agents Yes exactly but
secret very secret no one not even going
into this and I only want to work and I
know what is above and exactly it's yes
that the message came through which
is a very big sensation it's
made to trust someone with
a mallet after exactly are you quite sure
that's positive. This time it that's what
I think with the by the middle name did
nothing about this particular notes and I'm
quite sure to do everything for the smart
money amounts of. Rain. Well are you
crazy are you completely crazy you know
thank you God already big money amount for
you one come the funding for that was that
me yeah the spark or because you want to
get members of the good of all the.
Hello I think up my god a couple
hours with some of the boys out of
a hole in my head we go we can
easily look at my parents
because that's what's inside
of my dad I can't help it
I must know I have and I will spend
a detailed knowledge you know soon
as I get back I found and I really.
You do understand AND IT'S
IT'S
. I'll go
and find him and. A lot has I got
the.
The
.
I look like this. What is that how
far does the spank you put in the
shower if that's OK I'm
writing this is the only.
And the did I did. And I did I
thought an awful lot at least.
My English is the only.
Thing he has fighting with.
Ninety five thousand.
Yet isn't fighting with me but
me. Yeah yeah sure. But he goes
I found getting up with us by the back of.
The only.
The
on. The on.
on.
Laptop I think of how to get yes madam
but there's no label on the actual S.
And it's the I don't know who
just went to the station as my
name to call of course yes much. As I
love has them as it comes with one
hundred one thoughts thanks Jeff.
Oh the young lady yes madam this is the
end did you hear any hint that you think
you meant it seriously I believe
all right I just had a very
a call back home so if I don't check out
now it's goodbye to seeing the rest of the
law you have this trip anyway where you
go to Greece first I think I was leaving
this for you. Something to remember me by.
Because. This is. So beautiful. I.
Have. For you going I
haven't the faintest idea.
I thought you had
a good cry. Now I don't think
so why anything wrong I
mean to talk about your husband. I
haven't done any more but look on this
morning it'll mean you don't have to do it
so that we got
a lady. I can read you
couldn't that I couldn't
I mean I promised I wouldn't get in the
way or interfere with anything you wanted
to do but couldn't I mean shouldn't you
go back to England. I couldn't do it was
the least of all I'd be terrified to give
me time or answer for you if you missed
it that being. I came on.
Yes that yes look at it this is
actually been as just left said thing
yes it left the auto with the
mob and said You've got to.
Yes there are always stationed
with Madam. If you think.
God he's funny as
a god wouldn't know if you have done that
after all keep the fact that the drug
count of all of us in his column acting
he jumps ahead of us all the guy.
That.
Cannot understand. It's.
Your math upside down outside the down.
Metta feeling which nests never that go
getting ahead of them like that's with any
luggage and in all to get him on the
Greek terms yeah yeah before this is not
unusual get it into Turkey
that's a pending ask to make
a mess it's the see about that's
getting on the court and I'm like
a bag. You don't think is any danger this
man getting troops I don't get me that
line gets.
Not us cope with the US It was
a lot of the people the faces
of. Us here maybe Fed money
to just on
a phone bank but you know but I think the
specifics they need to increase is only
twelve months we're going to know what
happened kind of money that. Was.
You know the guns. Will. Come
here we're back to them. To.
Like even if it is what are you doing we
think makes me generally go home you go to
sees you mustn't you would be I don't see
some of the it's not going to say goodbye
to going to my son to get
a medal he's. The
. Darling boy. If you will of all people
of God comes out of heaven if it's to
collide with John after all I'm still going
to be how did you get here what
did Jesus referred to when I was
a bit what you end up like
a man and you know nothing about it you've
done an awful lot of cities like I was
attending going to put by sea ice and my
thanks to the orphanage that we could you
know about even though
they have never worked in
a mill all messages. Did you know then we
had Jamie you. Know if he
put his film with all of
our producers with the sixty of us.
What are the models about. Didn't know.
What to really you know we've got to prove
that it was we have not of the greatest
good because it is OK with that you
know. Just the enemy territory.
And the Democratic.
Party is finding much to plenty you might
think the smallest and now we do well
enough just.
Like. Well.
I suppose.
I'm on the cover of
a lot of you know but when the men
come to the biggest. Commitment
. You can count president he's trying
to stop it not going to be done that in
a couple of minutes but this isn't
enough. I've got to do it might not vote
but. You need to go through
with this one thing you
know the problem and I'm doomed
I've got to. Run. Going to go.
Build one.
That's
a good. Spot for
me today on the. Leash no
medical card I have to leave
Chicago town. Wishing you. All
I would be stuck in that.
CAR I. Hate being.
Now you can see.
Why on. Time and content
there for. A long.
It's an album like not
a new. Image from the film. I
better keep this and. See I don't trust.
Somebody's going on it's right. Here on
business all men are going to spy wreckage
to watch you cannot trust
and. I can place you know
a lovely big second wife. And I felt.
I was sorry for it. I'm sorry and.
Realize where you are. In
my country. And I mean.
Great two friends. On the train someone.
Has to make it on this train. They're
heading up my. Head.
And then. I try to find
to check what I'm going to do. But
you just have to have an evening.
I hope you're not bluffing I should ask
twenty seven allies you can guess that's
what. Wives tale hospice costs are
a full. On
assistant going up. I think best
business. For the villain was unmasked
today because. How did you find out about
me ask him and tell me when was because
I'm
a no different. Man. Right in the
biggest double crossing liar I've
ever met on.
Graduation. On a punctuality. Is
a mistake to take your time on account of
this I think you have the best you know
life.
That was. Fatal the enemy must have been.
Numerous German spies
which is. It's funny.
That I didn't live. There
with you. Know the kind.
That any. Legend You must live.
Well gentleman. Put on your mind and.
My fear but I guess people must be picked
apart from that in two thousand and six
weeks and I'm sorry but I had other
business to attend to for that over the
judgement. And now if
you. And this looks like.
It might affect you or I
congratulate you on. Especially.
One thing in spring. Anthony's great
week and. I think we can forgo the
thanksgiving service. Well. One of the
shooting began with God's sight will
be done this is my job to know.
That.
You cool with Madame conference we
finish up all your best. To him I
suggest not even I says he will just make
you feel as much at the end about what it
means what you think that makes his life
begin to live above listen to about him I
said I didn't. Have Time.
Thank. You.
General when freedom of speech.
And.